

# **CURRICULUM VITAE**

My name is Mattia Marsetti and I was born in the Alps. After playing with the famous bricks for almost a decade I dedicated my teens in mastering Latin and Greek, while self-teaching informatics. Then I found my way into Engineering and, at the same time, I felt the need to explore what was not modeled by an equation with various volunteering experiences. I'm currently working on the Powertrain SW that runs inside the Ferrari GT and Motorsport cars.

# E.

# **WORK EXPERIENCES**

MOTORSPORT SW SPECIALIST – Corse Clienti	2020 - now
SW Development, Integration and Testing	
Ferrari - Maranello	

2017-2020

2011-2016

POWERTRAIN CONTROL ENGINEER – GT Cars
Set up of the SW Sharing environment with the Supplier and SW
Development from Requirements to Tests
Ferrari - Maranello

MASTER DEGREE - Automation and Control Engineering



# **EDUCATION**

Politecnico di Milano - Milano	O	Ü		
► HIGH SCHOOL – Diploma di maturità Clas	ssica		2006-2	2011

# OTHER EXPERIENCES

Liceo G. Piazzi - Sondrio

VOLUNTEER	2014-2017
Phone operator & visits to the hospital for CasAmica - Milano	

REFUGEE EMERGENCY OPERATOR	LUG-AUG
logistics, transportations for CARITAS – Palermo	2014 - 2017
Integration project for a refugee family – Sondrio	

EDUCATOR
Kids education for Centro di Apojo Infanto Juvanil – Corumbà (Brazil)

LUG-AUG
2013



# **SKILLS**

- SW DEV. & DATA ANALYSIS: mainly Matlab/Simulink, often EXCEL, always GIT
- PLAN & PROCESS DEV: Agile Development in JIRA and SW Life-Cyle Development with Polarion
- CALIBRATION/DEBUG: expert in the use of CRETA INCA MDA ECU Diagnostics

## **CONTACTS**

(+39) 349 167 2584

marsigliomarsetti@gmail.com

Via Caggiati 2, Reggio Emilia (IT)

### ON THE WEB

in Linkedin

NO Twitter/Facebook/Instagram

#### LANGUAGES

ITALIAN

- native

**ENGLISH** 

fluent

## **INTERESTS**

Books and Comics
Board games
Analogue Photography
Snowboard

# PRIVACY

In compliance with the GDPR and the Italian Legislative Decree no. 196 dated 30/06/2003, I hereby authorize you to use and process my personal details contained in this document

Version: 1.27 - 15/08/20
Check out on GitHub